SUGANYA D

Senior Document Specialist

Contact



+91 7448587628



suganya290698@gmail.com



No:40/27 Annamalai Nagar, 2nd street, West mamalam, Chennai - 600033.

Skills

- A creative approach to problem solving
- Self-motivated and determined
- Adaptable and flexible
- Team work
- Leadership
- · Time management
- Honesty and integrity

Software

MS PowerPoint



MS Excel





Typing 60 WPM



English

Tamil

Hobbies

Languages





8

PROFILE

As a **Senior Document Specialist**, it is our responsibility to support the ongoing improvement and maintenance of a process for presentations and proposals that results in high-quality, accurate, and visually appealing presentations and proposals that meet or exceed the needs of internal and external parties.

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Create original graphic content for PowerPoint slides and Excel charts
- Setting up for meetings / PowerPoint presentations through requests
- Produce high-quality PowerPoint presentations according to the brand standard within tight deadlines
- Maintain the firm's brand and adhere to standard formatting
- Manage various resource databases
- · Build and troubleshoot template Word documents



EDUCATION

71% | Bachelor of Science in Computer Science SRI MUTHUKUMARAN ARTS & SCIENCE COLLEGE | 2018

72% | HSC

DR. K.K NIRMALA GIRLS HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL | 2015

82% | SSLC

DR. K.K NIRMALA GIRLS HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL | 2013



WORK EXPERIENCE

RR Donnelly

Document Specialist | May 2019 - Feb 2021

Williams Lea

Document Specialist | March 2021 - June 2022

RR Donnelly

Senior Document Specialist | June 2022 - Present